japandailypress.com 2019-10-30

# Privacy Policy

### What information do you collect?

We use cookies and/or web beacons as a myriad of other websites. This is usual practice and the idea is to generally provide you with a better experience as a reader. We also utilize these as a way to gather general visitor information and track visits our website receives. Cookies simply help us understand your preferences for subsequent visits in the future.

Keep in mind that you can disable cookies at any time through your browser options. Every browser has elaborated on the process to do so.

### What are cookies?

A cookie is a small text document often including an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it. However, to protect your privacy your browser only permits a site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or pass on computer viruses.

### Are you able to identify me in any way?

No. Cookies and the logs that we keep only log browser type, basic IP address information, operation systems and time stamps. We also don’t run any newsletter subscriptions. We don’t require any form of obligatory login or registration from you.

Thus said, please keep in mind that if you decide to participate in our comment section and reveal information about yourself, this data can be read and used by anyone who has viewed your comments. We are not responsible for any personal information you share on this website on your own.

As we – similar to most websites out there, use Google Analytics, you can opt out via the Google Analytics Opt Out browser plugin.

### Third Party Websites

JapanDailyPress.com’s articles may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to the respective third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We also cannot bear any responsibility in regard to the third party website’s content, privacy policy and general practices.

### Children Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)

As our products are targeted at adults, we do not specifically market any products to children under 13 years of age. When it comes to collecting personal information from children under 13, COPPA puts the child’s parents in control.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act

In line with CalOPPA, we assure you that you can visit JapanDailyPress.com anonymously. The privacy policy, once created, will be linked on the home page and every other page. It can be easily found and includes the word “Privacy” for maximum visitor awareness. Users will be notified of any policy changes on the Privacy Policy page.

### For questions

Should you have any questions in regards to your privacy, always feel free to reach out to us. We will do our best to reply as quickly as possible.

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any given time. Your continued use after we do so signifies you consent with abiding by the updated Privacy Policy. We will, of course, let you know of any Privacy Policy changes.
